peepow.com 2012-10-22

# - Peepow ...

**What is Peepow?**   
Peepow is a real artificial intelligence system that thinks by itself and discovers how things are related one to another.   
What's the next step ? Make it possible for a computer to actually think and understand, aiming to ease everyone's life. 

**Privacy Policy**

What information do we collect?   
We collect information from you when you register on our site or fill out a form, browse or search.   
Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

What do we use your information for?   
Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:   
; To personalize your experience  
(your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)  
; To improve our website  
(we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)  
; To improve customer service  
(your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)

Do we use cookies?   
Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information  
We use cookies to compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.

Do we disclose any information to outside parties?   
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

Third party links   
Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

Online Privacy Policy Only   
This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

Your Consent   
By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.

peepow @ peepow.com

This policy is powered by Free Privacy Policy and Rhino Support. Compare Rhino Support to Zendesk and save! 

**How to add my website to Peepow?**   
Use the link:   

**How to remove my website from Peepow?**   
To remove your link, send an email to: peepow @ peepow.com 

**How to remove a keyword from Peepow?**   
To remove your keyword, send an email to: peepow @ peepow.com
